What are you doing?
Why don’t you have breakfast before leaving?
I’m not hungry.
Um...
I looked into it yesterday,
the laws and culture of your planet.
It’s true, I was wrong.
I apologize to you.
Keep a one-meter distance from me.
Being angry will affect your magnetic field,
and bring you bad luck.
Annoying.
You’re here so early.
Isn’t this the normal time?
I was being sarcastic.
The meeting’s almost over, and now you show up.
Meeting?
What meeting?
Didn’t you schedule a meeting with Mr. Qin, the investor, today?
We agreed to meet.
But didn’t Mr. Jiang say the meeting was this afternoon?
When was it moved to the morning?
I don’t know.
Anyway, it started over an hour ago.
Mr. Qin, don’t worry.
We’ll make sure to improve everything according to your requests.
I trust Mr. Jiang to handle things well.
Where’s that young lady from last time?
Her?
She’s probably late.
Young people these days are always like that.
I’ll make sure to have a word with her later.
Alright then.
Let’s follow up in a couple of days.
Alright.
Sure, Mr. Qin.
Here’s the revised plan for 'Sweet Strike.'
Oh, I’m sorry, Mr. Qin.
What are you doing?
I’m so sorry.
The meeting’s already finished.
What’s the point of bringing this now?
What’s the use?
Mr. Qin,
please don’t be upset.
I instructed my assistant to inform her earlier.
Maybe the assistant forgot.
Anyway, that's my fault at work.
Please don't blame Qi Miao.
Qi Miao, is it?
You should learn from your teacher Jiang.
Punctuality is the most important thing for young people.
I'll head out now.
Take care, Mr. Qin.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Qin.
I promise this won't happen again.
Teacher Jiang.
I really didn’t receive any message.
About the meeting time change.
Maybe the assistant forgot.
Well...
What about my revised proposal?
Leave it there.
I'll pass it to Mr. Qin later.
If there's nothing else, please head out.
Sister Jianjian.
Where is Sister Jianjian?
She went to a concert today.
I'm watching the shop for her.
Are you her new assistant?
You look quite handsome.
By the way,
Do you need anything from Jianjian?
No, nothing.
I just wanted to ask how the jade is selling.
Alright then.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Hold on.
Have a seat.
What's the matter?
Sit down.
Here's the thing.
A couple of days ago,
A jewelry dealer came to the shop.
He said he was very interested in your jade.
Really?
And that dealer is quite generous.
He said he wants to buy all of your jade.
That's fantastic!
I knew it, I knew this time I'd make money!
Where is he?
I'll go find him.
Wait a second.
Now, here's the thing.
What is it?
The boss is planning to hold a jewelry exhibition soon.
You can always supply those jades and such.
But the issue is...
Right now, he wants to find a unique crystal.
He's searching everywhere for it.
Do you happen to have one?
Maybe?
A crystal.
Something like this.
This crystal looks so familiar.
Oh, right!
I have a crystal just like this at home.
Really?
What a coincidence!
But the thing is, this crystal isn't mine.
I'm pretty sure Brother Ruichi wouldn't want to sell it.
Actually, about that...
Selling isn't necessary.
The boss said...
As long as you're willing to rent it to him.
Just for a two-day exhibition, that's all.
And he’s offering a very generous price!
How much?
Five thousand?
Five hundred thousand.
Five...
Five hundred thousand?!
Is that for real?
He’s already put down a deposit.
Once the deal is done...
Not only will you get these gold leaves...
You’ll also receive the remaining five hundred thousand as a rental fee.
So, what do you think?
Not a bad deal, right?
Not bad, not bad at all.
I'll go talk to Brother Ruichi right now.
Hold on a second.
I’m not done yet.
Oh, please go on.
Here’s what I think.
With such a great opportunity...
Why do you feel the need to consult your friend?
And besides, they said...
It's just for one or two days.
Wouldn't it be better to keep all that money for yourself?
Sounds like it makes sense.
Don't worry.
I know exactly how to handle this.
I, Qi Dongdong, stand for just two words:
Reliability.
I promise to get you the crystal.
Well then, here's to a happy collaboration.
Happy collaboration, happy collaboration.
Richi bro!
Bro!
What's wrong?
Don't scare me like this.
I'm fine.
If you're fine, then why this gloomy vibe?
It's kind of creepy.
I just want some peace and quiet.
Bro.
Did you and my sister have a fight?
No.
I just made your sister upset.
Bro.
You are such a good man.
With that kind of awareness,
I'll help you.
How are you going to help me?
Well,
I remember you have a blue crystal.
Actually, my sister really likes things like crystals.
If you give her the crystal,
she'll definitely be happy.
No way.
Energy crystals are off-limits.
Think of another way.
Looks like borrowing the crystal is out of the question.
I'll have to think of another plan.
It's just that gifting a crystal is the easiest solution.
Anything else would be way too complicated.
As long as it works,
the process doesn't matter.
Alright then.
You're sure this will work?
Relax.
From my over 20 years
of experience making my sister angry,
if you use this trick,
it will absolutely work.
Alright, I'll listen to you.
Bro.
Can we take it easy next time?
No problem.
Qi Miao, why aren't you here yet?
Alan's concert is about to start.
Hurry up!
I just got off work.
I'm on my way!
Qi Miao.
President Qin is coming over for a meeting tomorrow morning.
Stay late and revise the new script.
But it's already seven o'clock.
If I start now,
how long will it take to finish?
President Qin really thinks highly of you right now.
You wouldn’t want to waste this opportunity, would you?
But I...
Just hang in there for a bit.
At the next meeting,
I'll give you lots of praise in front of President Qin.
Of course.
Qi Miao.
You just don't deserve,
any happiness at all.
This song,
is dedicated to,
you who fearlessly chase your dreams.
Even though you missed the concert,
happiness will always be with you.
May your dreams always burn bright.
I will.
You must be hungry.
I made some food.
You made all of this?
That's right.
I followed some tutorials.
It was pretty simple.
Qi Miao.
About what happened yesterday...
I'm sorry.
Since you helped me fulfill,
my dream of watching Alan's concert,
and even prepared such a feast for me,
I forgive you.
By the way,
you mentioned before that kissing me
was to replenish the crystal energy.
So why am I able to help you recharge your energy?
I’ve mentioned before,
we Lancans
can see other people's magnetic fields.
If we spend time with someone who shares the same magnetic field,
we can replenish each other's energy.
What if you meet
a lot of people with the same type of magnetic field at the same time?
On our Lanca planet, there's a vow,
if you meet someone with a matching magnetic field
and establish a bond,
you must stay together for life,
until death.
Establish a bond?
Yes, establish a bond.
It's what you Earthlings call marriage.
And the bonding process is the equivalent of your wedding night.
Men and women...
Stop, stop, stop!
If you keep going, it’s going to get inappropriate for kids!
But,
once bonded,
you must stay together forever.
Your planet is quite romantic, huh?
Isn't it the same on your planet?
If only it were like that.
Human emotions are incredibly complicated.
Forget it,
even if I explain it, you wouldn’t understand.
Here, drink.
Why is this drink so bitter?
You just don’t get it, do you?
Alcohol, despite tasting bitter,
can help you temporarily forget the things that make you sad.
Drink a bit more, and you’ll see.
Come on.
Another!
Alright!
As long as you’re happy.
Brother Ruichi.
Bro.
This is all the help I can give you.
Take this,
consider it a token of gratitude.